Good morning. I've got some responses to things people have said in the comments. But first,
I want to let you know that I will not be posting on Instagram this week. I have a lot of deadlines
that I have to hit. And if you see me missing, don't think I got hemmed up. It's because I'm
holed up in front of a computer. So I want to let you know that I will be posting to Patreon.
And you can check out my appearance that I did on MSNBC, as well as my commentary on that
appearance from last night on Patreon today. But let's get to these responses. Now, this is under
a post that Kevin Ortega, here's here's why Kevin posted. And someone said her apathy will lead us
astray. I want you to understand that the fact that people consider active challenging and active
questioning of the political landscape as apathy is their goal. They want you to feel like you
saying there's something better is you being apathetic when it's the exact opposite.
You believing in the fact that there is something better, believing in your own imagination and ability
to see something better. You looking at what is here and understanding it's not enough is the exact
opposite of apathy. It's actually a fertile ground for growth. She's talked too much and now I'm sure her
star is going to fade. Let me be clear. You cannot deny what you are, so you might as well accept it.
I have something that attracts people to me either in love or in hate. But it is what it is. And at some
point I decided I need to lean into that and do so living in truth. There is no star to fade
because I've been here this whole time. And nothing about this is based on your approval.
I would be a star if I had a scuba shop on a remote beach in Thailand. Stars are not based on
celebrity. They are based on people who give light and are the light in whatever space they're in.
If you don't want to miss my commentary on the things going on, for instance, D.C., the expansion
of the occupation, etc., make sure you watch Views from Amanda Land this Wednesday, 10 a.m. Eastern
on YouTube, Amanda Seals TV. Have a good Sunday, y'all.